daylife.com 2016-11-21

# Privacy Policy – NewsCred

California Residents

Last Updated: July 2015

NewsCred values and respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes the types of personal information we collect, how we use the information, with whom we share it, and the choices you can make about our collection, use and disclosure of the information. We also describe the measures we take to protect the security of the information and how to contact us about our privacy practices.

#### Information We Collect

NewsCred may obtain personal information about you from various sources, including our websites (including websites we operate on behalf of our clients), when you call or email us, communicate and/or engage with content through social media, or when you participate in events or other promotions. We also may obtain information about you from our business partners, clients and other third parties.

##### Types of Information

When you visit and interact with our websites and/or our customers’ websites, certain information may be collected via a cookie, including:

  1. your computer's Internet Protocol (IP) address;

  2. your browser type and operating system;

  3. search terms that you use to reach the site;

  4. the web pages you were visiting immediately before and after you came to the site;

  5. dates and times of visits to the site;

  6. information on actions taken on the site (such as page views and site navigation patterns);

  7. amount of time spent viewing certain pages or screens;

  8. standard server log information;

  9. social actions taken with respect to the content on the site, including but not limited to Likes, Shares, Tweets, Retweets, Favorites and Pins on LinkedIn, Facebook, Twitter and Pinterest; and/or

  10. advertisement interaction and viewing data, such as ad click-through rates and information about how many times you viewed a particular ad.

Please note that NewsCred’s website and our customers’ websites may contain links to other websites and gather data from social media sites, including LinkedIn, Facebook, Twitter and Pinterest. We recommend that you read the privacy policies of the aforementioned sites and every website that you visit. We are not responsible for those sites’ privacy practices.

When you visit our websites and/or our customers’ websites, NewsCred and our customers may also collect information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or online services. Because there is not yet a consensus on how companies should respond to web browser-based or other do-not-track ("DNT") mechanisms, we do not respond to web browser-based DNT signals at this time.

##### Inferred Data

We may combine the information we collect with information we receive from our business partners, clients and other third parties. Types of data we may infer about you consist of:

  1. name and title;

  2. company;

  3. geographic location;

  4. demographic information, such as industry type;

  5. social media metrics and scores;

  6. interests; and/or

  7. URLs you have shared on social media.

#### How We Use Your Information

In order to learn more about how our websites are used, we aggregate and analyze the data that we collect. We may use this information, for example, to monitor and assess use of the website, to increase our websites’ functionality, and to better tailor our content and design to suit our visitors' needs.

Cookies help us to improve our websites and to deliver a better and more customized service. They enable us:

  1. to estimate usage numbers and patterns;

  2. to store information about your preferences, and to allow us and/or our customers to customize our and their respective websites according to your individual interests;

  3. to analyze and enhance our and/or our customers’ marketing communications and make them more relevant;

  4. to speed up your searches; and

  5. to recognize you when you return to our website and/or our customers’ websites.

NewsCred and/or our customers may use combined information to enhance and personalize your online experiences, to communicate with you about products, services and events that may be of interest to you, and for other promotional purposes.

We also may use the information we obtain about you in other ways for which we provide specific notice at the time of collection.

##### Business Communications

You may provide your email address to us or other contact information to receive industry news, intelligence, information about NewsCred products and services, and other business communications. You may opt out of our email marketing communications using the link at the bottom of each email. Please note that even if you opt out, you may continue to receive certain email communications from us regarding your relationship with NewsCred, such as updated in our site terms.

#### Business Transitions

In the event NewsCred goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

#### Disclosure

We may share the information we maintain about you with our service providers, business partners and clients. NewsCred also may need to disclose personal information when required by law and/or when we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a) a current judicial proceeding, b) a court order or c) legal process served on NewsCred.

If you participate in certain features of this website (e.g., sharing content), please note that any information you voluntarily disclose through use of these features becomes available to the public and/or to other users whom you have designated.

#### Information Security

NewsCred has technical, administrative and physical safeguards in place to help protect against unauthorized access to, use or disclosure of user information we maintain. We recognize, however, that no program is one hundred percent secure and we cannot guarantee that our safeguards will prevent every unauthorized attempt to access, use or disclose personal information. If you become aware of a security issue, please email us at privacy [at] newscred [dot] com. We will work with you to address any problems.

#### Your Rights and Choices

You may opt out of cookies on NewsCred’s websites and our customers’ websites by downloading the plugin located at <https://www.ghostery.com/en/download>. However, if you refuse cookies, you may be unable to access certain parts of these websites or be unable to use some of our and/or our customers’ services.

You may withdraw any consent you previously provided to us, or object at any time on legitimate grounds, to the processing of your personal information, including the sharing of your information with third parties, by emailing privacy [at] newscred [dot] com. We will apply your preferences going forward. In some circumstances, withdrawing your consent to NewsCred's use or disclosure of your personal information will mean that you cannot take advantage of certain NewsCred products or services.

#### Data Transfers

This is a U.S. website subject to U.S. laws, including those governing the privacy and security of your information. When we obtain personal information about you, we may process the information outside of the country in which you are located, including in the United States. The countries in which we process the information may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you are located. We will protect your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

#### U.S - EU Safe Harbor

NewsCred complies with the U.S. – EU Safe Harbor framework and the U.S. – Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data from European Union and European Economic Area member countries and Switzerland. NewsCred has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. Please see NewsCred’s Safe Harbor Policy for more details.

#### Your California Privacy Rights

If you are a California resident, you may request that we provide to you (i) a list of the categories of personal information about you that NewsCred has disclosed to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes during the calendar year preceding your request, (ii) the names and addresses of such third parties, and (iii) if the nature of the third parties’ business cannot reasonably be determined from their names, examples of the products or services marketed, if known to NewsCred, sufficient to give you a reasonable indication of the nature of the third parties’ business. To submit your request, please email privacy [at] newscred [dot] com, with the subject line "California Privacy" and your request in the body of your email.

#### Notification of Changes

Whenever NewsCred changes this Privacy Policy, we will post the updated Privacy Policy on this page and change the “Last Updated” date above so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

#### Contact Information

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please feel free to send an email to privacy [at] newscred [dot] com, call (212) 989-4100 or send a letter by mail to Privacy Officer, NewsCred, Inc., 386 Park Avenue South, 6th Floor, New York, NY 10016.

Facebook-outlineIcon of a facebook-outlineFacebookIcon of a facebookGoogle-plusIcon of a google-plusHamburgerIcon of a hamburgerInstagramIcon of a instagramLinkedinIcon of a linkedinMailIcon of a mailPinterestIcon of a pinterestTwitterIcon of a twitterVenmoIcon of a venmoVideoIcon of a videoYoutubeIcon of a youtube
